Jared Scarr

Seattle, WA

jaredscarr@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jaredscarr | github.com/jaredscarr | jaredscarr.com

I am a full stack developer with a strong background in end-user customer experience. I am focused on writing customer-centric and results driven code that bring solutions to the market and a company's bottom line.

Technical Skills

Python, Django, REST, S3, EC2, CloudFront, Route53, Ansible, Pyramid, JavaScript, JQuery, GitHub, Foundation 6, HTML, CSS, JSON, Postgresql, AJAX, PostGis

Projects

Cocktail Inventory API, October - current 2016 | github.com/jaredscarr/bartrack

- Developed a RESTful API with the Pyramid framework
- Stores inventory and provides cost information

Portfolio, May - August 2016 | jaredscarr.com

- Designed a single page application using the Foundation 6 framework
- Deployed on Amazon Web Services with EC2, CloudFront and Route 53 DNS

RideShare, May 1 - 5, 2016 | github.com/RideQuest/rideshare-backend

- Utilized a PostGIS spatial database and Google Maps to connect users based on their proximity to each other
- Built a RESTful API for front end consumption with the Django Framework

Work Experience

Software Developer, GMB Fitness, Seattle, WA

Sep 2016 - Jan 2017

- Migrating videos and metadata from one cloud storage site to another
- Writing scripts in Python to automate the transfer

Manager / Lead Instructor, Foundation CrossFit, Seattle, WA

Sep 2012 - Nov 2016

- Led athletes to achieve their goals in a strong, positive team culture
- Developed an innovative program that increased maximum capacity of athletes by 50%
- Piloted and organized events for charity and promotions

Bartender, Seattle WA

May 2004 - Jan 2015

- Contributed to the creation of products for menus and events
- Redesigned the bar to improve rate of production
- Trained new hires in the proper execution of cocktails and service

Education

Code Fellows, Seattle, WA

Nov 2015 - May 2016

Python Advanced Development Certificate, May 2016